<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Ray-Man Advance # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Ace Combat Advance</name>
		<desc>The Ace Combat series makes its debut on the Game Boy Advance with challenging missions, unlockable planes, and free-roaming environments. As the newest pilot in an elite fighter squadron, you must help destroy the Air Strike Force--the military arm of an evil multinational corporation. If you destroy enough enemy planes during your missions, you'll unlock new planes. Fly in air-to-air and air-to-ground missions over arctic, forest, and desert environments. Each environment features destructible buildings and objects.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ray-Man Advance # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aero the Acrobat - Rascal Rival Revenge # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Aero the Acrobat</name>
		<desc>Aero the Acrobat, the classic Sunsoft game for Super NES, comes to Game Boy Advance! Edgar Ektor (and evil ex-circus clown) has booby-trapped the circus with the help of a crazy flying squirrel named Zero and his fairground henchmen. Only Aero, a master of acrobatics, can diffuse the dangers of the circus and perform various death defying acts to amuse the unsuspecting audience. As the headlining act, Aero will walk tightropes, swing on trapezes, blast out of cannons and plunge off the high dive in order to find Ektor and put a stop to his evil plans. 
Great graphics and action-puzzle elements garnered Aero the Acrobat great reviews when it was first released in 1993. Now you can re-live the classic on Game Boy Advance.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Aero the Acrobat - Rascal Rival Revenge # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Metro 3D</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Hominid # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Alien Hominid</name>
		<desc>He's been shot at, shot down, stolen from and probed. It's time to get even.

The game is a side-scrolling shooter in a similar vein to games like Metal Slug, where one hit instantly kills, and can be played simultaneously with one or two players. Players play as the titular hominid who has to fend off waves of secret agents. His main arsenal is a blaster, while players can also melee close-up enemies and use a limited number of grenades. Advanced moves include rolling under shots, jumping on and biting off enemies' heads, temporarily scaring other enemies, and digging underground and dragging enemies down with them.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Alien Hominid # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tuna</developer>
		<publisher>Zoo Digital Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Astro Boy - Omega Factor # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Astro Boy: Omega Factor</name>
		<desc>Join Astro, the robotic superhero with a human mind, in a quest to reunite the robotic race with humans. Astro uses his seven super abilities to face off against the likes of Atlas, Blue Knight, and more than 40 other characters. The game brings classic 2D gaming to the Game Boy Advance along with an original seven-episode story. Playing as Astro Boy, you'll learn about justice, compassion, evil, courage, and the history of Astro Boy--all while building Astro's Omega Factor and strengthening his character and superhuman abilities.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Astro Boy - Omega Factor # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040817T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Atari Anniversary Advance (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Atari Anniversary Advance</name>
		<desc>Atari presents 6 of the best arcade games ever made, mega-hits that launched the video game revolution -- Asteroids, Battlezone, Centipede, Missile Command, Super Breakout and Tempest. Each game is reproduced down to the last detail, and each one is just as easy and fun to play. Whether you're a diehard fan or a competitive newcomer, you've got to play the games that started it all!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Atari Anniversary Advance (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo Kazooie - Grunty's Revenge # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie: Grunty's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Gruntilda is back, and it's up to Banjo and Kazooie to stop her master plan. In Banjo-Kazooie: Grunty's Revenge, you'll play as Banjo and follow him through six worlds rife with trials and contests. Some of the challenges you must overcome include solving puzzles, avoiding obstacles, and battling different enemies. Defeat your foes by using Banjo's array of combat moves. You can also seek help from witch doctors, who can transform Banjo into a mouse, a tank, and other creatures.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Banjo Kazooie - Grunty's Revenge # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo Pilot # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Banjo-Pilot</name>
		<desc>Banjo Pilot is a kart-style racing game which was originally slated to become "Diddy Kong Pilot." It features at least eight characters from the Banjo-Kazooie series, each with its own aircraft and storyline, including Banjo, Mumbo Jumbo, Humba Wumba, Guntilda, Klungo, Jolly Roger and Kazooie. The game includes link cable support for up to four players.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Banjo Pilot # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Max 2 - Red (E) (M3).gba</path>
		<name>Bomberman Max 2 Red Advance</name>
		<desc>Bomberman again teams up with Max to take on the evil Mujoe. But before they get the chance, Mujoe turns the tables, shrinking the heroes into tiny critters. Now the two must use their bombing powers and traverse the levels, blowing up obstacles and enemies to get to the exit, to eventually destroy the device and return themselves to normal size.

As with all previous Bomberman title, the aim of the game is to plant bombs, destroying anything that come within the boundaries of the blast. Charabomb characters can be collected during play to increase your powers, or you battle and trade them with a friend in link mode.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Bomberman Max 2 - Red (E) (M3)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Max 2 - Blue (E) (M3).gba</path>
		<name>Bomberman Max 2: Blue Advance</name>
		<desc>Bomberman and Max have been shrunk to the size of an ant by the evil Mujie's secret weapon. Work together with max to find and destroy the device before Mujoe can take control of the universe. And so the newest adventures of Bomberman begins!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Bomberman Max 2 - Blue (E) (M3)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomber-Man Tournament # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Bomberman Tournament</name>
		<desc>An S.O.S. from the cosmos signals that planet Phantarion is in trouble! Grab your arsenal and get ready for non-stop action as you blast your way through interactive battlefields and take on up to 4 real-time players. Battle opponents through 8 interactive battlefield mazes! Take on up to 4 players in multi-player blastfests! Fast, furious, explosive bombing adventure!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Bomber-Man Tournament # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20010626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire II (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire</name>
		<desc>Long ago in the days of darkness and magic, a young wanderer comes face to face with his destiny. You control the fate of Ryu, a young warrior and descendant of the Light Dragon Clan. Together, with your mystical friend, Nina, you must search for magic spells and mysterious secrets. Along the way, gain experience and skill as you battle against strange monsters. Uncover valuable secrets that will help you on your adventure and unlock the secrets of the Dragon Clan.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Breath of Fire II (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20011213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire (E) (M3).gba</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire</name>
		<desc>Long ago in the days of darkness and magic, a young wanderer comes face to face with his destiny. You control the fate of Ryu, a young warrior and descendant of the Light Dragon Clan. Together, with your mystical friend, Nina, you must search for magic spells and mysterious secrets. Along the way, gain experience and skill as you battle against strange monsters. Uncover valuable secrets that will help you on your adventure and unlock the secrets of the Dragon Clan.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Breath of Fire (E) (M3)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20011213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Broken Sword - the Shadow of the Templars # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Broken Sword: The Shadow of the Templars</name>
		<desc>Adapted from one of the most popular PC games in Europe, Broken Sword: The Shadow of the Templars is the story of George Stobbard, an American in Paris who witnesses the theft of an ancient manuscript and the assassination of its owner. This manuscript was created in the 14th century by the order of the Knights Templar and points to where their legendary power has been hidden for more than 600 years. Its new owners intend to harness the power for their own sinister agenda. This version of the game re-creates the original's graphic-novel look, puzzles, locations, and characters, as well as the original soundtrack, while the interface and the game's control system is being redone to Game Boy Advance specifications.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Broken Sword - the Shadow of the Templars # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Revolution Software</developer>
		<publisher>BAM! Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Car Battler Joe (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Car Battler Joe</name>
		<desc>Rampaging rogues roam the highways and byways that surround your village. If your believed the rumors, you would blame your missing father for the surge in vehicular violence. That's why you've decided to lead the life of a car battler, transporting cargo between towns and running down every lethal lead foot foolish enough to cross your path. This gritty work isn't easy. Other car battlers fight for money or fame, but you have a higher calling: You're determined to restore your family's lost honor and bring your father home.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Car Battler Joe (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ancient</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Aria of Sorrow (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow</name>
		<desc>Aria of Sorrow features a 2D side-scrolling style of gameplay where the player controls the onscreen character from a third-person perspective to interact with people, objects, and enemies. Like previous games in the series and most role-playing games, characters level up each time they earn a set number of experience points from defeating enemies; each "level" gained increases the character's statistics, thus improving their performance in battle. Statistic examples include hit points, the amount of damage a character can receive; magic points, which determine the number of times a character can use magical attacks; strength, the power of a character's physical attacks; and intelligence, the power of a character's magical spells. Upon encountering an enemy, the player can use a variety of weapons to attack and defeat the enemy. Despite the game being set in 2035, the available weapons are largely medieval, including swords, axes, and spears; though a handgun is available. These weapons differ in their damage output, the range of the weapon, and the speed of the attack. Items and other accessories can be found by defeating enemies or by purchasing items from the game's shop.

Similar to previous games in the series, Aria of Sorrow is set within Dracula's castle, which is further subdivided into several areas that the player traverses. These areas feature different components, such as different enemies, varying terrain characteristics, and a unique piece of theme music. Similar to most platform games, progression between areas is limited by the abilities the player currently has.[12] While the method in which the player progresses through the game is initially linear, the player's options become more diverse as the number of character abilities increases.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - Aria of Sorrow (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Circle of the Moon # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Circle of the Moon</name>
		<desc>Count Dracula has been resurrected and evil will reign supreme unless he is stopped. As Nathan Graves, you'll hunt down the count and use your whip and a variety of special items to destroy his minions. Battle your way through Dracula's castle and rid the world of evil once and for all!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - Circle of the Moon # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Harmony Of Dissonance # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Harmony of Dissonance</name>
		<desc>Harmony of Dissonance is set in the fictional universe of the Castlevania series. The premise of the series is the eternal conflict between the vampire hunters of the Belmont clan and the immortal vampire Dracula. Harmony of Dissonance takes place in 1748, fifty years after Simon Belmont defeated Dracula's curse. A result of Simon's fight against Dracula was that the villagers changed their opinion of him and the Belmont family.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - Harmony Of Dissonance # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20020916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami TYO</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chu Chu Rocket! # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>ChuChu Rocket!</name>
		<desc>The object of the game is to guide one or more mice ("ChuChus") around a board into one or more goals while avoiding cats ("KapuKapus") roaming the board. The mice and cats all move in predictable paths by always turning right when hitting a wall head on, by following corners or by turning around when in a dead end.

ChuChu Rocket!'s multiplayer mode revolves around up to four players placing arrows on the level at once, trying to direct mice into their own rockets and cats into other players' rockets (any cat that reaches a rocket removes a percentage of the mice within). Each player can only have three arrows on-screen at a time and cannot place them on other players' arrows or their own arrows. Arrows would disappear over time, or could be removed by a player placing his fourth arrow (which would eliminate the first arrow placed, thus leaving three). Although a simple concept, this quickly becomes frenetic with the relentless speed of the mice and four players fighting over them.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Chu Chu Rocket! # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot 2 - N-Tranced # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot 2: N-Tranced</name>
		<desc>Crash is back and ready to take on an all-new nefarious villain. After the events of Crash Bandicoot: The Huge Adventure, Tropy, with the help of N. Trance, kidnaps Coco and Crunch, planning to brainwash them to the evil side. Now, Crash must travel to N. Trance's twisted realm, battle and rescue Coco and Crunch, and ultimately defeat N. Trance and N. Tropy. To achieve these goals, you must use all of Crash's spin, slide, and jumping abilities across 24 different levels. As you progress through the game, you'll find yourself flying a helicopter, water-skiing, and piloting a spaceship--all for the sake of saving your friends.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Crash Bandicoot 2 - N-Tranced # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030615T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot - Purple Riptos Rampage # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot Purple: Ripto's Rampage</name>
		<desc>In Crash Bandicoot Purple: Ripto's Rampage and Spyro Orange: The Cortex Conspiracy, Dr. Neo Cortex--Crash's nemesis--and Ripto--Spyro's nemesis--have accidentally met up through underground portals and are set on taking over the entire universe. Crash and Spyro must team up with each other to discover the identity of the new menace and save the universe from this evil plot. In these side-scrolling adventures, you can link up with three friends for a variety of multiplayer modes, including Party Games, Wager Games, and Card Trading. Connecting both Crash Bandicoot Purple and Spyro Orange gives you the option of unlocking special content and allows you to trade and wager the cards with friends.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Crash Bandicoot - Purple Riptos Rampage # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot - the Huge Adventure # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot: The Huge Adventure</name>
		<desc>Tired of endlessly doing battle with meddling bandicoots, the nefarious Dr. Neo Cortex shrinks the entire Earth, and Crash and Coco along with it, to the size of a wumpa fruit. Luckily, Coco invents a machine to reverse the effects, but she needs crystals from around the world to power it. Crash must retrieve the crystals to help return the entire planet to its natural state. Experience Crash's biggest adventure yet, with gameplay modes ranging from side-scrolling to 3D chase levels to aerial dogfight combat sequences. Battle your way through over 20 huge levels and six unique locations to defeat Cortex and save the world.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Crash Bandicoot - the Huge Adventure # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Denki Blocks! (USA) (En,Es).gba</path>
		<name>Denki Blocks!</name>
		<desc>The people of Puzzle Island love to play puzzle games. Their favorite is Denki Blocks! A game of skill that is played by sliding blocks around a board, joining colored blocks together to build shapes and solve puzzles.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Denki Blocks! (USA) (En,Es)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20011030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rage Software</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Games</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney's Kim Possible 2 - Drakken's Demise (U).gba</path>
		<name>Disney's Kim Possible 2: Drakken's Demise</name>
		<desc>Kim Possible's new adventure leads her into battle with Falsetto Jones, Gemini, Duff Killigan, Shego, and Dr. Drakken in four intense episodes. In each new episode, Kim gains gadgets and acrobatic abilities that allow her to bounce up walls, judo-flip henchmen, reflect laser beams, and spray hot sauce to melt icy obstructions. If all else fails, you can engage her stealth suit and make her invisible to enemy eyes. Once Kim acquires new gadgets and abilities, you can then replay earlier levels to access areas that were previously unreachable.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Disney's Kim Possible 2 - Drakken's Demise (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artificial Mind and Movement</developer>
		<publisher>Buena Vista Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lilo &amp; Stitch # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Disney's Lilo &amp; Stitch</name>
		<desc>WARNING: Stitch is extremely dangerous. The result of an illegal genetic experiment by a mad scientist, Stitch appears to be harmless - small, furry, with six legs - but his very existence is an abomination to all that's decent in the galaxy. Last seen on the island of Hawaii in the company of a little girl named Lilo. Fugitive may be disguised as a family pet.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Lilo &amp; Stitch # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 2 (U).gba</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 2</name>
		<desc>The Donkey Kong Country series returns to the Game Boy Advance in a sequel that features Dixie Kong. She and Diddy Kong must team up to rescue Donkey Kong from the evil Kaptain K. Rool. You'll play as both Diddy and Dixie, and master their different attacks. Test your skills and beat the clock in Diddy's Dash, or race against your friends to see who's the fastest. You can play the game solo or challenge your friends in new bonus games such as Funky's Flights and Bag a Bug.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Donkey Kong Country 2 (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20041115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 3 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 3: Dixie Kong's Double Trouble!</name>
		<desc>Revisit Donkey Kong Island and join the Kong family for their latest adventure. The Kremlings have a mysterious new leader named KAOS and are up to their usual mischief, even capturing Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong. Now it's up to Dixie Kong and the newest Kong, a giant infant named Kiddy, to rescue the two missing apes.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Donkey Kong Country 3 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 3: Dixie Kong's Double Trouble!</name>
		<desc>Revisit Donkey Kong Island and join the Kong family for their latest adventure. The Kremlings have a mysterious new leader named KAOS and are up to their usual mischief, even capturing Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong. Now it's up to Dixie Kong and the newest Kong, a giant infant named Kiddy, to rescue the two missing apes.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Donkey Kong Country # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong - King of Swing # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 3: Dixie Kong's Double Trouble!</name>
		<desc>Revisit Donkey Kong Island and join the Kong family for their latest adventure. The Kremlings have a mysterious new leader named KAOS and are up to their usual mischief, even capturing Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong. Now it's up to Dixie Kong and the newest Kong, a giant infant named Kiddy, to rescue the two missing apes.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Donkey Kong - King of Swing # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dr. Mario &amp; Puzzle League # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Dr. Mario &amp; Puzzle League</name>
		<desc>Dr. Mario/Puzzle League are recreations of two of Nintendo's most popular puzzle creations. Though Dr. Mario has already been released on the GBA as a Classic NES Series title, the version included in the dual-pack is enhanced specifically for the Game Boy Advance hardware instead of a straight emulation of the original NES title. Puzzle League was originally brought to life as Tetris Attack, but then rebranded on the Game Boy Color as Pokemon Puzzle Challenge a few years back. The GBA version is also enhanced for the GBA's much more capable graphics hardware.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Dr. Mario &amp; Puzzle League # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Drill Dozer # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Drill Dozer</name>
		<desc>In the platformer Drill Dozer, you can take the roll of Jill, the daughter of a crime boss who is set on revenge. When a rival gang steals away her family's heirloom, Jill gives chase in her Drill Dozer, an upgradeable piece of power armor equipped with a large drill. This piece of equipment will help you navigate through six different areas, where you will encounter varied enemies and bosses.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Drill Dozer # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20060206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem Advance (U).gba</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem Advance</name>
		<desc>Alien scientists have taken control of the top-secret Area 51 military base, and are plotting to overthrow Earth! But not if Duke can stop them. Armed with alien-busting weapons, his kick-butt attitude, and using the aliens' own transporters, Duke takes the battle to four unique locations around the world. Oh, and rescues a few babes along the way.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Duke Nukem Advance (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20020813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3D Realms</developer>
		<publisher>Take-Two Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ecks vs. Sever (E) (M5).gba</path>
		<name>Ecks vs. Sever</name>
		<desc>An FBI agent and a rogue NSA agent are pitted against each other in a deadly game of cat and mouse. Both skilled assassins bent on personal revenge, each must terminate the other in order to survive. But unknown to each other, they are both pawns in a much larger conspiracy. Now the as the hunters become the hunted, they must both determine who the real enemy is.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ecks vs. Sever (E) (M5)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crawfish</developer>
		<publisher>BAM!</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero - Maximum Velocity (USA, Europe).gba</path>
		<name>F-Zero: Maximum Velocity</name>
		<desc>Maximum Velocity takes place a twenty-five years after Captain Falcon, Dr. Stewart, etc "piloted their way to fame". Due to the aforementioned, it is the only F-Zero game without Captain Falcon, Samurai Goroh, Pico, or Dr. Stewart. However, one of the F-Zero cars resembles Falcon's Blue Falcon. The pilot, Kent Akechi, also claims to be Falcon's son.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/F-Zero - Maximum Velocity (USA, Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nd Cube</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>F24: Stealth Fighter</name>
		<desc>Intelligence reports indicate that Iran is looking to conduct offensive air operations within the No Fly Zone. As an F24 fighter pilot you must eliminate the enemy, rescue international leaders and secure diplomacy in the Middle East.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Skyworks Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Games</publisher>
		<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy - Tactics Advanced # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics Advance</name>
		<desc>When Marche and his friends open an ancient magical tome, their small town is transformed into a fantasy-filled kingdom known as Ivalice. Now, Marche must take up the sword and master the arts of war if he has any hope of returning home. Guide Marche and his clan against countless foes in tactical combat and discover the wonders of Ivalice. How will you restore your town to normal...and do you even want to?</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Final Fantasy - Tactics Advanced # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight One (U).gba</path>
		<name>Final Fight One</name>
		<desc>Classic arcade action is unleased on the Game Boy Advance system in Final Fight One. There's trouble in Metro City. The members of the Mad Gear Gang have kidnapped the mayor's daughter Jessica and the clock is ticking. The mayor, an ex-street fighter himself, calls in the big guns to help, enlisting the iron fist team of Cody and Guy. Now, it's a race against time to scour the city, defeat an army of the Mad Gear Gang's minions, and rescue Jessica before it's too late!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Final Fight One (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20010926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sun-Tec</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem</name>
		<desc>The rightful heir to the throne of Rikea is finally returning home after many years lost to her people. But before the celebrations can begin, you must first guard her through the evil lands that await before you, by taking charge of an elite group of soldiers possessing skills unlike any other.

The first Fire Emblem title to be released outside of Japan includes an all new quest featuring a selection of warriors, wizards and dragons (both good and bad). Battle through turn-based environments and choose your moves wisely, as those you lose during a fight will be lost for good.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Fire Emblem # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem - Fuuin no Tsurugi (J) [T+Eng10.2_Dark Twilkitri].gba</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem: Fuuin no Tsurugi</name>
		<desc>Fire Emblem: Fūin no Tsurugi is a turn-based tactical role-playing game in which players move a small group of units around a square-based grid, battling their enemies in order to complete a certain predefined objective. It is reminiscent of other tactical RPGs with features such as character classes and the ability to level up.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Fire Emblem - Fuuin no Tsurugi (J) [T+Eng10.2_Dark Twilkitri]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20020329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem - the Sacred Stones # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem: The Sacred Stones</name>
		<desc>In Fire Emblem: The Sacred Stones, you must help protect the nation of Renais from the invading Grado Empire. Plan your strategy, choose your units, and then lead your soldiers in to battle. The more experience your soldiers gain, the more you can upgrade their abilities. This time, your soldiers can gain experience by fighting new monsters in the Tower of Valni.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Fire Emblem - the Sacred Stones # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050323T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frogger's Adventures 2 - The Lost Wand (E) (M5).gba</path>
		<name>Frogger's Adventures 2: The Lost Wand</name>
		<desc>Frogger's Adventures 2: The Lost Wand is an Adventure game, developed and published by Konami, which was released in 2002.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Frogger's Adventures 2 - The Lost Wand (E) (M5)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frogger's Adventure - Temple of the Frog # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Frogger's Adventures: Temple of the Frog</name>
		<desc>Firefly Swamp is dying and the frogs from the Elder Council have asked Frogger to save it! To do so, Frogger must undertake a grueling quest to collect the sacred elements needed to keep the swamp alive. These elements have been stolen by the evil Mr. D and have been spread throughout four perilous worlds. Frogger must travel to each world retrieve the stolen elements and defeat Mr. D's evil henchmen. Then and only then will he be able to enter the Temple of the Frog to face the treacherous Mr. D.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Frogger's Adventure - Temple of the Frog # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Game &amp; Watch Gallery Advance # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Game &amp; Watch Gallery Advance</name>
		<desc>Anthology of classic Nintendo games
Includes remakes of Donkey Kong 3, Mario Cement Factory, Rainshower, Boxing, and Fire Attack
More games can be unlocked by scores
View games in original LCD style or updated colour versions
For 1 or 2 players</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Game &amp; Watch Gallery Advance # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<developer></developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Golden Sun</name>
		<desc>Golden Sun is the first original role-playing game for the Game Boy Advance to appear in the U.S. And despite perhaps a too-familiar story line, Golden Sun's jaw-dropping graphics, deep magic system, and unique multiplayer arena mode truly show that the Game Boy Advance is capable of a serious RPG.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Golden Sun # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20011111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun - The Lost Age (USA, Europe).gba</path>
		<name>Golden Sun: The Lost Age</name>
		<desc>The story of Golden Sun: The Lost Age picks up right near the end of the first game. Golden Sun veterans will be surprised to learn that The Lost Age is played from the point of view of the party being chased as they try to light the remaining two lighthouses, which will unlock the power of alchemy for the world--or will it instead unlock the world's destruction?</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Golden Sun - The Lost Age (USA, Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius Galaxies (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Gradius Galaxies</name>
		<desc>The classic franchise Gradius comes to Game Boy® Advance! An evil force has taken over a distant star system and only you can stop them. Soar through a myriad of enemy attack units and blow them to bits using ultra powerful weapons including photon missiles and laser beams.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Gradius Galaxies (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20011112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mobile21</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto Advance # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto Advance</name>
		<desc>Grand Theft Auto Advance brings the thrills of the class GTA gaming series to your Game Boy Advance. In this all-new revenge-driven story, you're on the run from the cops after being framed for murder. You were set to do one last job for Vinnie, a local mob boss - until his car blew up, taking his life and all the cash he was paying you. You're the prime suspect and every cop in Liberty City is after you -- but you're not leaving until you can find out who set you up and shut them down.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Grand Theft Auto Advance # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse Software</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunstar Super Heroes # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Gunstar Super Heroes</name>
		<desc>Taking place after the destruction of the "God of Ruin" (also known as Golden Silver, the final boss) at the end of Gunstar Heroes, the explosion created four moons orbiting the Earth. However, many years later, the creation of a fifth moon reveals a plan to resurrect the malevolent Empire and Golden Silver once again.

Most of the new characters bear both the names and likenesses of their equivalents in the original game (such as Blue, Yellow, Green, Pink, Kain, Kotaro, Orange, Black, Gray, and Smash Daisaku). The main characters combat the Empire under the organization called The Third Eye, (abbreviated "3YE") under the names Red (female in the North American version, ambiguous in the Japanese) and Blue in recognition and tribute to the characters from the original game, and along with Yellow on the team, they are known as Gunstar Super Heroes. The Gunstars must travel to the moons, stop the resurrected Empire, and recapture the Treasure Gems, four mystical stones with an unknown power that had driven the story in the last game. The game has different storylines based on what difficulty is chosen and which character the player is playing as.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Gunstar Super Heroes # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure Co. Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hamtaro - Ham-Ham Games (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).gba</path>
		<name>Hamtaro: Ham-Ham Games</name>
		<desc>Put your athletic skills to the test with Hamtaro and his Ham-Ham pals as they compete in the 2004 Ham-Ham Games. You must guide different Ham-Hams to victory in 15 sporting events; including archery, sprinting, sailing, swimming, and more. Root for your favorite Hamtaro characters as they go head-to-head with new Ham-Hams, such as the pirates of Team Seaham. Also, with the Game Boy Advance Game Link Cable, you can trade statistics and collectible costumes with your friends.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Hamtaro - Ham-Ham Games (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)-image.png</image>
		<developer></developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon - Friends of Mineral Town # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon: More Friends of Mineral Town</name>
		<desc>Live the simple life as a farmer in Harvest Moon: More Friends of Mineral Town. This game is similar to the original Harvest Moon: Friends of Mineral Town, but now you can play as a girl who has left the city to pursue a life on the farm. You'll take part in growing crops, managing livestock, finding a husband, and raising children.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Harvest Moon - Friends of Mineral Town # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon - More Friends of Mineral Town (U).gba</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon: More Friends of Mineral Town</name>
		<desc>Live the simple life as a farmer in Harvest Moon: More Friends of Mineral Town. This game is similar to the original Harvest Moon: Friends of Mineral Town, but now you can play as a girl who has left the city to pursue a life on the farm. You'll take part in growing crops, managing livestock, finding a husband, and raising children.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Harvest Moon - More Friends of Mineral Town (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Karnaaj Rally (U).gba</path>
		<name>Karnaaj Rally</name>
		<desc>Leave a trail of destruction behind as you blast ahead of the competition. Make your opponents spin and crash as you bombard them with a barrage of weapons. Take them out of the race with rockets and mines. Win races and prize money so you can progress to the next level of competition for more fire action.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Karnaaj Rally (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paragon 5</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters EX 2 - Howling Blood # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>King of Fighters EX 2: Howling Blood</name>
		<desc>In The King of Fighters EX 2: Howling Blood, you can play as or against 21 characters from the King of Fighters series, including three characters that are exclusive to this version. Each new match gives you an opportunity to refine your fighting skills, unlock secrets, and master powerful moves. If you need help during a match, you can call on your partner to temporarily fight by your side. Perfect your fighting strategy in a variety of gameplay modes, such as 3-VS-3 Battle, two-player VS, and Story.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/King of Fighters EX 2 - Howling Blood # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters EX, The - NeoBlood (U) (V1.1).gba</path>
		<name>King of Fighters EX: Neo Blood</name>
		<desc>Invitations to the King of Fighters Tournament have been sent to the best fighters in the world by an unknown host. Despite suspicions of an evil scheme, the fighters are ready to enter the arena to determine who the true King of Fighters will be.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/King of Fighters EX, The - NeoBlood (U) (V1.1)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20021105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts - Chain of Memories # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts: Chain of Memories</name>
		<desc>The game takes place in Castle Oblivion, a mysterious castle kept by Marluxia. Sora and his teammates are told that the castle causes visitors to lose their memories upon entering. The lobby and areas between floors are white with flower-themed decorations, but each floor can be transformed into a different world from the first Kingdom Hearts game using "world cards" created from Sora's memories. Like before, many of the worlds are based on Disney films while the rest were created by Square Enix.

Unlike the previous game, the worlds are created from Sora's memories. As such, many of the events experienced in Kingdom Hearts are relived in this game; Sora encounters memory-based versions of Disney characters that he has met before. The individual plotlines differ from those in the original game and revolve around the theme of memory. The exception is the Deep Jungle world which does not reappear in Chain of Memories. Just as Kingdom Hearts had several worlds created specifically for that game, Chain of Memories introduces Twilight Town, in addition to the original worlds of Kingdom Hearts. The world card for Twilight Town was created from memories on "the other side of Sora's heart".</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Kingdom Hearts - Chain of Memories # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby and the Amazing Mirror # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Kirby &amp; the Amazing Mirror</name>
		<desc>There is a Mirror World that exists in the skies of Dream Land. It is a world where any wish reflected in the mirror will come true. However, one day it only copies evil minds, and rapidly changes into a world of evil. Meta Knight notices this, and flies up to save the Mirror World.

Meanwhile, Kirby is taking a walk when Dark Meta Knight appears. Before Kirby can react, Dark Meta Knight slices Kirby in four and Kirby becomes four different colored "Kirbys". Kirby travels alone, but if his cell phone is working, he can call his friends and they will help him. They chase after the Dark Meta Knight and enter the Mirror World.

The two Meta Knights fight each other and the real Meta Knight is defeated. He is knocked into the mirror, which is then cut into eight fragments by Dark Meta Knight (which are then scattered across the mirror world), so Kirby must save Meta Knight and the Mirror World. After collecting all eight mirror fragments, Kirby enters the Mirror World and battles Dark Meta Knight. After defeating him, a vortex appears and sucks Kirby in, who is given Meta Knight's sword. Kirby fights 4 bosses before battling the Dark Mind. Upon defeat, the Mirror World is saved.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Kirby and the Amazing Mirror # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040415T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flagship</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby - Nightmare in Dreamland (U) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Kirby: Nightmare in Dreamland</name>
		<desc>This remake features updated graphics and sound, as well as some minor changes to the gameplay, new mini-games, and the ability to play as the character Meta Knight (in a mini-game called "Meta Knightmare"). Also, Nightmare in Dreamland allows for cooperative multiplayer with 2-4 players, all of whom play as different-colored Kirbies.

After Kirby wakes up from his after-lunch nap without having any dreams, he goes to the Fountain of Dreams to investigate. In doing so, he discovers that King Dedede has stolen the Star Rod, the source of power to the Fountain of Dreams, and broken it into seven pieces, giving six fragments to his allies, Whispy Woods, Paint Roller, Mr. Shine and Mr. Bright, Kracko, Heavy Mole, and Meta Knight, also keeping one for himself. Without the Star Rod, all of the inhabitants of Dream Land are becoming restless and unable to dream. Kirby decides to track down the fragments of the Star Rod and bring them back to the Fountain of Dreams in order to restore everyones' dreams.

Kirby travels throughout seven worlds, battling enemies, mini-bosses, and bosses through treacherous terrain in order to collect all seven fragments of the Star Rod. Once Kirby defeats King Dedede and rebuilds the Star Rod, he places it back into the Fountain of Dreams. However, an ominous black aura fills the skies as a dark creature named Nightmare who emerges from the fountain. It turns out that Nightmare had corrupted the fountain, and King Dedede removed the Star Rod, broke it, and spread it across Dream Land with the intention of protecting Dream Land. Nightmare then flies off into space, and King Dedede inhales Kirby and the Star Rod and spits them into the air. Kirby then uses the Star Rod to defeat both forms of Nightmare, and saves Dream Land once again.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Kirby - Nightmare in Dreamland (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klonoa 2 - Dream Champ Tournament # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Klonoa 2: Dream Champ Tournament</name>
		<desc>Klonoa 2: Dream Champ Tournament takes place sometime after the events of Klonoa: Empire of Dreams. The game begins shortly after Klonoa defeats the King of Despair, and receives an invitation letter that floats from the sky telling him that he has been selected to compete in the prestigious "Dream Champ Tournament" among other accomplished adventurers for the title of "Greatest Hero" as well as a cash reward. After Klonoa finishes reading, he is enveloped in a bright light and finds himself transported inside a gigantic arena alongside several other adventurers. He meets up with Lolo and Popka, only to learn that they are taking part in the competition as well, and a pompous rogue named Guntz who brushes him off immediately. The master of ceremonies, and sponsor of the tournament itself, Garlen, makes his appearance and informs everyone that they will be paired off in a single-elimination tournament that has them racing across several worlds of his own choosing. The first one to reach the end will be the winner and will advance to the next round.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Klonoa 2 - Dream Champ Tournament # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klonoa - Empire of Dreams # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Klonoa: Empire of Dreams</name>
		<desc>Taking place after Klonoa 2: Lunatea's Veil, Klonoa: Empire of Dreams follows the adventures of Klonoa after he awakens one morning in the Kingdom of Jillius, and is dragged by the emperor's royal guards to his throne room for seemingly no reason. Emperor Jillius himself informs Klonoa that he broke the sacred law of his kingdom by dreaming, which he views as a worthless endeavor and a total waste of time. The Emperor himself suffers from insomnia, and decrees that if he cannot be allow to dream, then no one can. Rather than punish Klonoa outright, he instead offers him a challenge: defeat the four great monsters that are wreaking havoc on the land, and he will be set free. Joined by his friend Huepow, Klonoa has no choice but to travel to the surrounding lands and do battle with the monsters living there, hoping to earn his freedom and bring peace to the kingdom at last.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Klonoa - Empire of Dreams # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Konami Krazy Racers (Europe).gba</path>
		<name>Konami Krazy Racers</name>
		<desc>Race your favorite Konami characters through 16 action packed, fun-filled courses on your way to the checkered flag! 16 challenging courses showcase the power of hame Boy Advance graphics, including Cyber Field, Ice Paradise, Pop 'n Beach, Skybridge, and many more! 8 Classic Konami characters to choose from, including Ninja from Metal Gear Solid, Dracula of Castlevania fame, and Goemon the Mystical Ninja.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Konami Krazy Racers (Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCEK</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kuru Kuru Kururin # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Kuru Kuru Kururin</name>
		<desc>The story begins when Kururin’s brothers and sisters go missing, and it is up to him to find them. Kururin is initially unsure that he is up to the task because he has never left his home world before. Being the adventurous and helpful fellow he is, Kururin agrees to rescue his lost family. Teacher Hare trains Kururin in the art of controlling the Helirin, a stick-shaped helicopter that has a slow-spinning propeller. Piloting the Helirin through the different worlds will be a difficult task, but using Teacher Hare's valuable lessons, Kururin bravely sets out on his adventure to rescue his lost family.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Kuru Kuru Kururin # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kururin Paradise (Japan).gba</path>
		<name>Kururin Paradise</name>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Kururin Paradise (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<developer></developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LEGO - Star Wars - the Video Game # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars: The Video Game</name>
		<desc>Lego Star Wars blends Lego toys with the characters, stories, and vehicles from the prequel eras of the Star Wars universe. Now you can experience scenes from The Phantom Menace, Attack of the Clones, and Revenge of the Sith while controlling characters such as Obi-Wan Kenobi, Yoda, and Anakin Skywalker. Use the Jedi "force" to solve puzzles and manipulate environments. During your journey, you'll do everything from pod racing on Mos Espa to repelling the droid onslaught in the Genosian arena. Your friend can even join the action to help you at any time during your game.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/LEGO - Star Wars - the Video Game # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ray-Man 3 - Hoodlum Havoc GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Lizzie McGuire 3: Homecoming Havoc</name>
		<desc>With Homecoming rapidly approaching, Lizzie is determined to be crowned Homecoming Queen. Of course, Lizzie's archrival Kate wants the crown too. In order to win the affection of the student body and become popular enough to become Homecoming Queen, Lizzie will need to complete over 100 different speed challenges, plus compete in dance-offs with Kate to win the title. Players will build friendships to get past obstacles and gain popularity points on the way to the homecoming dance.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ray-Man 3 - Hoodlum Havoc GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar Legend (U) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Lunar Legend</name>
		<desc>You play Alex, a young boy who hopes to one day be a Dragonmaster like his dearly departed hero Dyne. One day, a wizard named Nash comes into town, and needs an escort to a nearby shrine in the woods. You, your childhood friend Luna, and your flying cat-like pet Nall accompany Nash to the shrine, and your adventure begins.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Lunar Legend (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magic Rings</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario and Luigi - Superstar Saga # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Superstar Saga</name>
		<desc>An evil witch has replaced Princess Peach's fair speech with explosives! Mario and Luigi must once again come to her rescue, but this time they employ the help of Bowser, their sworn enemy. Mario and Luigi must learn new moves and combine powers to fight off enemies and move closer to the witch's castle. Guide this unlikely bunch through an abundance of minigames such as Border Jump and Mystery Carts. Combine the powers of Mario and Luigi to pull off special tag-team moves. Immerse yourself in this bright, cartoonish, and humorous world, complete with hit music featured in previous Mario games.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario and Luigi - Superstar Saga # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AlphaDream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Golf - Advance Tour # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mario Golf: Advance Tour</name>
		<desc>Grab your clubs and start down the road to golfing perfection in this role-playing golf adventure! Chat up the locals at golf clinics, hone your skills in challenges like Club Slots and Go-Go Gates, and try to become the champ of all the country clubs! The Mushroom Kingdom residents take on only the very best.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario Golf - Advance Tour # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20040622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart - Super Circuit # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mario Kart: Super Circuit</name>
		<desc>As was the case with its predecessors, Super Circuit is a circuit racing game. In it, the player races against seven opponents, each of which is a character from Nintendo's Mario series, in small go-karts, on tracks set in the Mario universe. Power-ups, strewn across each track, aid the bearer or hinder their opponents, as well as coins; the coins increase the player's top speed.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario Kart - Super Circuit # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Tennis - Power Tour # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis: Power Tour</name>
		<desc>Following in the footsteps of other portable Mario Sports titles, Power Tour adds a bit of RPG-like features into the mix of standard tennis action. Story mode has you guide either one of the rookie players, Max or Tina, through the ranks of competitors in the academy on their way to the Island Open Championships. Winning matches against opponents in the academy rewards you with points you can use to raise your stats. Matches can either be in one-on-one Singles matches, or you can team up with an AI-controlled partner in Doubles.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario Tennis - Power Tour # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario vs. Donkey Kong # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>After years of apparent goodwill, Mario and Donkey Kong are at it again--this time, on Game Boy Advance. Donkey Kong has stolen all the Mini-Mario toys from the Mario Toy Co., and now it's up to Mario to hunt down his longtime nemesis and retrieve the pilfered goods. As Mario, you must race through challenging levels while finding keys and releasing Mini Marios before time runs out. Along the way, you'll master new moves that can help you overcome new puzzles.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario vs. Donkey Kong # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20040524T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Max Payne (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Max Payne</name>
		<desc>Max Payne is a man with nothing to lose--a fugitive undercover cop framed for murder, and now hunted by the cops and the mob. As Payne, you'll uncover plot twists, engage in dramatic "bullet-time" firefights with thugs, and fight your way through an unforgiving New York blizzard. Max can wield a variety of weapons including pistols, submachine guns, shotguns, sniper rifles, grenades, and Molotov cocktails. Prepare yourself for an involving story combined with slick action.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Max Payne (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mobius Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Medal of Honor - Infiltrator (U) (M3).gba</path>
		<name>Medal of Honor: Infiltrator</name>
		<desc>Medal of Honor Infiltrator puts you in the role of Corporal Jake Murphy, a man who must complete five daring missions to defeat the Axis powers in WWII. From sabotaging enemy resources to capturing key personnel to all-out firefights, you'll need to master a variety of gameplay styles to overcome the enemy. On foot, in a tank, or even in disguise, you must engage opponents on the battlefield with an assortment of WWII-era weapons, including machine guns, grenades, bazookas, and more.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Medal of Honor - Infiltrator (U) (M3)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20031117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Netherock</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man and Bass # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man &amp; Bass</name>
		<desc>The story of Mega Man &amp; Bass varies slightly depending on which player character is chosen. It begins when a robot villain named King breaks into Dr. Wily's laboratory and then the Robot Museum to collect the data blueprints for the creations of Dr. Light. Dr. Light alerts the hero Mega Man that he must go at once to the Robot Museum to confront this new enemy. Meanwhile, Bass (Mega Man's rival and Wily's greatest creation) hears of the new criminal's appearance and decides to prove himself the stronger robot by defeating King. Proto Man is the first to arrive at the scene. King divulges his plan to him; he desires to create a utopia in which robots rule the world over humans. To accomplish this, King seeks to create an unstoppable army using the data and invites Proto Man to join him. Proto Man refuses and attempts to attack, but King counters and slices his body in half. Proto Man then teleports back to the lab for repairs while King escapes with the data. With their own motivations, Mega Man and Bass set out to put a stop to King's plans.

After vanquishing eight powerful robots under allegiance to King, the duo infiltrates his castle and engages him in combat. Proto Man interrupts the fight and again attempts to defeat their new nemesis. Putting all of his remaining energy into a blast, Proto Man manages to destroy King's shield and loses consciousness, allowing Mega Man and Bass to best King in battle afterwards. King questions why they fight so hard for humans when robots are the superior species. The pair explains that humans are the ones who created robots in the first place, which confuses King. The villain reveals that his creator is Dr. Wily, who then appears on a video monitor. When King asks the evil inventor why robots fight each other for the sake of humans, Wily strengthens his "brainwashing level" and restores his power. Mega Man and Bass engage King in another battle and defeat him. The castle begins a self-destruct sequence and the protagonists escape without King.

Mega and Bass begin a final confrontation with Dr. Wily in his newly-regained laboratory. When Wily is beaten, Bass demands to know why he deceived him. Wily explains that he created King simply to test Bass' abilities because of his past failures in challenging Mega Man. Wily shows him written plans for making a newer version of King to join with Bass in this venture, promising that the two would be invincible together. Proto Man appears and immediately destroys these plans. Proto Man tells Bass that although he is a strong robot of free will, he can never defeat his rival because he has nothing for which to fight. Mega Man returns home where his sister Roll presents him a letter from King. King wishes to atone for his own crimes against humans and hopes for them to be friends if they were meet in the future.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man and Bass # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 2</name>
		<desc>Enter the futuristic universe of Mega Man.EXE in this new adventure in the Battle Network series. Join him in his battle to fight cyber crimes in this mega role playing adventure. Now, there's a new net crime organization in town and its computer hacking has created a virus that's quickly gaining momentum. It's up to Mega Man.EXE, his pal Lan and friends to join the Net-Battlers and win this new cyber battle. Stop it before it spreads!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network 2 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 2</name>
		<desc>Enter the futuristic universe of Mega Man.EXE in this new adventure in the Battle Network series. Join him in his battle to fight cyber crimes in this mega role playing adventure. Now, there's a new net crime organization in town and its computer hacking has created a virus that's quickly gaining momentum. It's up to Mega Man.EXE, his pal Lan and friends to join the Net-Battlers and win this new cyber battle. Stop it before it spreads!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network 2 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network 3 - Blue # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 3: Blue Version</name>
		<desc>Join Mega Mega.EXE, his pal Lan and friends as they keep the net safe from cyber mayhem in the most expansive battle network adventure yet. Together with the White version, find all of Mega Man's battle style changes, "Giga Class" Chips, enemies and discover more surprises just for you!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network 3 - Blue # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network 3 - White # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 3: White Version</name>
		<desc>Join Mega Mega.EXE, his pal Lan and friends as they keep the net safe from viruses and cyber menaces. You'll travel through new virtual and real worlds, fight-off new bosses, interact with new characters and even find new Battle Chips. It's cyber mayhem at it's best!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network 3 - White # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network 4 - Blue Moon # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 4: Blue Moon</name>
		<desc>The fourth installment in the Mega Man Battle Network series comes in two versions--Red Sun and Blue Moon--each with different enemies, battle chips, souls, and characters. Once again, you assume the role of Lan as he and his friend, Mega Man.exe, fight to rid the Internet of viruses and other cyberworld enemies. Unlike previous games in the series, Mega Man Battle Network 4 focuses on a tournament system where players encounter a variety of enemies that must be defeated. A new Soul Unison system lets Mega Man transform into his defeated enemies.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network 4 - Blue Moon # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network 4 - Red Sun # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 4: Red Sun</name>
		<desc>The fourth installment in the Mega Man Battle Network series comes in two versions--Red Sun and Blue Moon--each with different enemies, battle chips, souls, and characters. Once again, you assume the role of Lan as he and his friend, Mega Man.exe, fight to rid the Internet of viruses and other cyberworld enemies. Unlike previous games in the series, Mega Man Battle Network 4 focuses on a tournament system where players encounter a variety of enemies that must be defeated. A new Soul Unison system lets Mega Man transform into his defeated enemies.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network 4 - Red Sun # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 2</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network 5 - Team Colonel # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 5: Team Colonel</name>
		<desc>Team Colonel is the second edition of Mega Man Battle Network 5. In the game, you can join forces with characters from previous installments of the Mega Man Battle series, and you can play in a new fighting mode. Team up with other cyberheroes in an effort to stop an evil organization from taking control of the global Internet.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network 5 - Team Colonel # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network 5 - Team Proto-Man # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 5: Team Protoman</name>
		<desc>Team Protoman is the first edition of Mega Man Battle Network 5. In the game, you can join forces with characters from previous installments of the Mega Man Battle series, and you can play in a new fighting mode. Team up with other cyberheroes in an effort to stop an evil organization from taking control of the global Internet.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network 5 - Team Proto-Man # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network 6 - Cybeast Falzar # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 6: Cybeast Falzar</name>
		<desc>In Mega Man Battle Network 6, Lan's father has received a job transfer and the family moves to Cyber City, a town known for conducting various technological experiments. Lan will meet new people and build new friendships in the real world while Mega Man befriends helpful Navis and encounters dangerous new enemies on the virtual plane. Together they will face threats far more powerful and perilous than they ever have before.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network 6 - Cybeast Falzar # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man Battle Network 6 - Cybeast Gregar # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle Network 6: Cybeast Gregar</name>
		<desc>In Mega Man Battle Network 6, Lan's father has received a job transfer and the family moves to Cyber City, a town known for conducting various technological experiments. Lan will meet new people and build new friendships in the real world while Mega Man befriends helpful Navis and encounters dangerous new enemies on the virtual plane. Together they will face threats far more powerful and perilous than they ever have before.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man Battle Network 6 - Cybeast Gregar # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man - Zero 2 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 2</name>
		<desc>Set one year after the events of the first game, Neo Arcadia still actively hunts Zero, and the battle comes to a head out in the desert. Zero survives the assault, but collapses soon afterward, and is rescued (oddly) by Harpuia. He is brought back to the Resistance Base, where he meets the new leader of the Resistance, Elpizo. Zero assists in various missions against Neo Arcadia, but Elpizo becomes mad with power with the baby elves, copies of the Dark Elf. Elpizo eventually revives the Dark Elf by finding and destroying X's physical body, which acted as a seal. As Elpizo powers up with 2 baby elves and the revived Dark Elf, Zero confronts and defeats him. Elpizo is transformed to a cyber-elf and flies away, while Cyber-elf X appears, explaining the origins of the Dark Elf to Zero.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man - Zero 2 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20030502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man - Zero 3 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 3</name>
		<desc>Two months have passed since Elpizo turned mad with power and freed the Dark Elf by destroying the body of the original X. Ciel has finally finished her research on a new energy supply, and Zero is leading a group towards Neo Arcadia to make peace at last. However, readings similar to the Dark Elf emanate from a snow field, and they stop to investigate. Inside a gigantic spaceship that fell from orbit, Zero discovers a massive Reploid, Omega, and the enigmatic Dr. Weil, the one X spoke of when talking about the curse of the Dark Elf. It seems Weil isn't alone this time, either - he has built a new Copy X, and together, the two of them instate a new regime in Neo Arcadia. Zero eventually destroys Omega. While fighting him, he finds that (apparently) his body was merely a copy, while Omega had Zero's true form. Weil, trying to tempt him with this fact, didn't turn out successful. Zero killed Omega with the help of the remaining 3 guardians (Harpuia, Leviathan, Fefnir) and The Dark Elf breaks free of her curse completely, ending the game.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man - Zero 3 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20040423T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-Man - Zero 4 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 4</name>
		<desc>Not long after the defeat of Omega, Weil now has a malicious objective and has taken hold of Neo Arcadia as the dictator and replacing the Pantheons with his own personal fleet of "Variants". Weil unfairly infringes upon citizen's rights, both reploid and human. Tired of the oppression from Neo Arcadia, humans migrate to a location known as Area Zero in hopes of starting a new life.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mega-Man - Zero 4 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20050421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Slug Advance # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Metal Slug Advance</name>
		<desc>Now you can have all the 2D arcade action of Metal Slug in the palm of your hand, because Metal Slug Advance has arrived on the Game Boy Advance. Through five action-packed missions, you must move out on foot or in slug vehicles across rugged terrain and underwater bases. Your objective is to rescue hostages by destroying enemies and solving strategic puzzles. Completing your missions becomes easier when you collect more than 100 types of E-cards, which enhance your character's abilities.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metal Slug Advance # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory</developer>
		<publisher>SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid - Fusion # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Metroid Fusion</name>
		<desc>Bounty hunter Samus Aran, the protagonist, explores the surface of the planet SR388 with a survey crew from Biologic Space Laboratories (BSL). She encounters an X Parasite, virions that can replicate their hosts' physical appearances and memories, killing them afterward. Samus is unknowingly infected by the virus, and proceeds to return to the BSL station, when she suddenly loses consciousness and is ejected from her ship before it crashes into a nearby asteroid belt. The Galactic Federation recovers her body and discovers that the X Parasite infected Samus's central nervous system. They counteract the parasite's damage by creating a vaccine using Samus's cellular sample from the remains of a Metroid that Samus previously contacted. The vaccine cures Samus and also gives her Metroid-like characteristics, including the ability to absorb and use the nuclei of X Parasites for nourishment, and the Metroid's vulnerability to extremely cold temperatures. Her infected Power Suit is sent to the BSL station for examination, although parts of the suit are bonded to her body and cannot be removed, forming a partially-armored suit known as the eponymous Fusion Suit. The Federation sends Samus to investigate an explosion aboard the BSL station. While there, she learns that the space station is swarming with organisms that are infected with X Parasites. A group of X Parasites manage to recover and use components of Samus's infected Power Suit to transform into the SA-X, a form of the parasite that partially mimics Samus at full power and possesses the Ice Beam that can exploit Samus's weakness to cold temperatures. Samus escapes from the SA-X before it attacks her, and continues exploring the space station. She discovers a restricted lab, which the Galactic Federation is secretly using to breed Metroids. Suddenly, the SA-X appears once again, and attempts to destroy the lab, with itself in it. Samus narrowly escapes the lab before it is destroyed, and later learns that the SA-X managed to asexually reproduce before perishing, subsequently cloning itself. In addition, Samus learns that the Galactic Federation plans to capture the X and the SA-X for further study. Samus is certain that the Federation underestimates the destructive power of the X Parasites, and takes it upon herself to destroy the BSL station by setting it on a collision course with SR388. As she prepares to exit the station, she encounters an Omega Metroid, which proceeds to destroy one of the SA-X. Samus absorbs the nucleus of the SA-X and uses her newly-restored Ice Beam to destroy the Omega Metroid, before escaping to her ship, which extracts her from the space station before it collides with SR388.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metroid - Fusion # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo Research &amp; Development 1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid - Zero Mission # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Metroid: Zero Mission</name>
		<desc>Space Pirates attack a Galactic Federation-owned space research vessel and seize samples of Metroid creatures. Dangerous floating organisms, Metroids can latch on to any organism and drain its life energy to kill it. The Space Pirates plan to replicate Metroids by exposing them to beta rays and then using them as biological weapons to destroy all living beings that oppose them. While searching for the stolen Metroids, the Galactic Federation locates the Space Pirates' base of operations on the planet Zebes. The Federation assaults the planet, but the Pirates resist, forcing the Federation to retreat. As a last resort, the Federation decides to send a lone bounty hunter to penetrate the Pirates' base and destroy Mother Brain, the mechanical life-form that controls the Space Pirates' fortress and its defenses. Considered the greatest of all bounty hunters, Samus Aran is chosen for the mission. Samus lands on the surface of Zebes and explores the planet, traveling through the planet's caverns. She eventually comes across Kraid, an ally of the Space Pirates, and Ridley, the Space Pirates' commander, and defeats them both. Along the way, Samus finds and destroys Mother Brain. However, while Samus leaves the planet in her gunship, it is attacked by Space Pirates, causing it to crash back on to Zebes, near the Space Pirate Mothership. Exploring the Mothership, Samus eventually reaches the Ridley Robot, a mechanized form of Ridley. After defeating it, Samus escapes the planet using one of the Space Pirate's shuttles, while the Mothership self-destructs.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metroid - Zero Mission # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Rancher Advance (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Monster Rancher Advance</name>
		<desc>Monster Rancher Advance is a Strategy Role-Playing game, developed and published by Tecmo, which was released in 2001.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Monster Rancher Advance (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Rancher Advance 2 (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Monster Rancher Advance 2</name>
		<desc>Monster Rancher Advance 2 lets players create, train, and fight with monsters of their own choosing. Monsters are generated by inputting key phrases to create different monsters. Each phrase entered will create a unique monster, which will always appear when that specific phrase is entered. Players can experiment with many different phrases for unexpected results. Two separate monsters can also be combined with special items to form an entirely new monster. Certain combinations will lead to hidden, rare monsters which can not be obtained through the normal monster generation process.

The Coaching System from Monster Rancher Advance has been dramatically improved for added depth in the sequel. Depending on the monster type, certain coaches will offer unique training sessions which other monster coaches will not be able to provide. These special training sessions can be very difficult and dangerous, yet have potential to yield major results. A monster's charisma and skills will also be crucial factors in deciding whether it is suitable to be a good coach or not. Coaches will now recognize and alert you to certain warnings which your breeding assistant may not notice.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Monster Rancher Advance 2 (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat - Deadly Alliance (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).gba</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat: Deadly Alliance</name>
		<desc>A controversial franchise marks its return in Mortal Kombat: Deadly Alliance. This time around, the fighting game features an all-new fighting system, an in-depth, supernatural storyline, and the infamous brutal fatalities. Beginning the next chapter in the battle of good versus evil, two powerful sorcerers--Shang Tsung and Quan Chi--join forces to deliver unrivaled fighting action in their quest for supreme mortality. Use new or classic Mortal Kombat fighters and engage in hand-to-hand and special-weapon combat, executing secret moves and combinations for fatalities and deadly body blows.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mortal Kombat - Deadly Alliance (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Games</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mother 3 (J) [T+Eng].gba</path>
		<name>Mother 3</name>
		<desc>Mother 3 starts out very differently from the first two Mother games as is it divided up into eight different chapters, similar to Dragon Quest IV. Instead of focusing on a group of children, it chronicles the story and adventures of Lucas and his family, and the story switches perspective during each chapter. For example, the first half of the game is played as Flint, Duster, and Salsa, but the rest of the game is played as Lucas. The Nowhere Islands also change dramatically due to the influence of the Pigmask Army, transforming from a simple low-tech rural society to a more modern twenty-first century infrastructure that's similar to the first two Mother games (hence the game's theme of nature vs. technology). The game also features a more traditional top-down RPG perspective, instead of the oblique projection used in the first two games.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mother 3 (J) [T+Eng]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo | HAL Laboratory | Brownie Brown</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Cop # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Ninja Five-O</name>
		<desc>Take on the role of Ninja Five-O as he uses all his skill, stealth and magic to rescue hostages and defeat his enemies. Master the art of ninja swords, shuriken throwing stars and ancient ninjitsu magic!

* Kaginawa Wire grappling hook that can be used to hang, fly, jump, climb walls and surprise attack.
* 6 Challenging missions covering 20 levels.
* Crush objects to find hidden Power-Ups and secret items
* Unique enemy boss characters for each level.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ninja Cop # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030415T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pac-Man Collection # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Pac-Man Collection</name>
		<desc>One of the first video games ever created, PAC-MAN still happens to be one of the best, as well. This comprehensive collection includes three unique Pac-Man titles in one complete package. Inside you'll find the original Pac-Man which has you traversing mazes, avoiding deadly ghosts, and chomping down nutritious dots; Pac-Mania is a 3D take on the first version, in which you can actually jump over the ghosts; and Pac-Attack is a Tetris-like experience that'll have you lining up blocks in a fast-paced environment.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pac-Man Collection # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mass Media</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pocky &amp; Rocky with Becky # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Pocky &amp; Rocky with Becky</name>
		<desc>An evil Hydra Dragon has been awakened from a long sleep and has unleashed the world's most fearded mythical creatures on the land. It is up to you to stop them and eventually put an end to the evil Hydra's madness! You can choose one of the three characters, Pocky, Rocky the Raccoon or Becky to embark on this fantastic and dangerous adventure. Collect magical items and a variety of power-ups to help battle the mythical bosses as you journey to the final showdown with the Hydra!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pocky &amp; Rocky with Becky # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Altron</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Fire Red # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Pokemon Glazed</name>
		<desc>Twelve years ago, you were born in a small town in Tunod region. Today is your birthday and usually, like other boys in the town, you will receive your first Pokemon. It will be your friend forever and protect you. But if you are hurry for a journey, you can be in dangerous. You must have the best preparation before making a journey in Tunod. You don’t know what is ahead you. The news on TV talks about a mysterious power that wants to deface your world and Pokemon World. Also you will wonder about a mysterious team around the ancient ruins.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon - Fire Red # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GameFreak</developer>
		<publisher>RedRiders180</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Red Rescue Team # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Pokemon Mystery Dungeon Red Rescue Team</name>
		<desc>Are you Ash Ketchum in this game? NO! you've been turned into a POKEMON! Help save the Pokemon world with your newly found pokemon skills.  Gameplay is similar to the previous games except of course the glaring fact that you aren't a trainer anymore.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Red Rescue Team # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Pinball - Ruby &amp; Sapphire (E) (M5).gba</path>
		<name>Pokemon Pinball Ruby &amp; Sapphire</name>
		<desc>Pokemon Pinball has all the features you'd demand of a pinball game, including bonus tables, lots of bumpers and ways to score massive points. As with your standard videogame pinball game, the left button on the D-pad and the A-button control the flippers with the R/L triggers used to shake the table. The catch here is that everything is themed in Pokemon. Instead of a ball, you make use of a Pokeball. Instead of standard bumpers, you're hitting the Pokeball against other Pokemon, and the ultimate goal is of course to "catch 'em all". The game features 200 Pokemon, two main tables, and link cable support.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon Pinball - Ruby &amp; Sapphire (E) (M5)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jupiter</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Emerald Version (USA, Europe).gba</path>
		<name>Pokémon Emerald Version</name>
		<desc>Pokemon Emerald Version is a sister game to Pokemon Ruby and Sapphire, and is the fifth and final Generation III main series game. Like its predecessor, Pokemon Crystal, it added many features not present in the earlier paired versions.

It was the second highest selling video game of 2005 in North America. It was also the third best-selling game for the Game Boy Advance, losing to its two predecessors, Ruby and Sapphire and FireRed and LeafGreen. Emerald was the final main series game released on the Game Boy line of handhelds.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon - Emerald Version (USA, Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Ruby Version (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Pokémon Ruby Version</name>
		<desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokemon Ruby. This entry in the Pokemon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokemon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokemon Ruby is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokemon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokemon contests. With new Pokemon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokemon Sapphire takes the Pokemon experience to the next level.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon - Ruby Version (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Leaf Green Version (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Pokémon Sapphire Version</name>
		<desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokemon Sapphire. This entry in the Pokemon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokemon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokemon Sapphire is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokemon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokemon contests. With new Pokemon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokemon Sapphire takes the Pokemon experience to the next level.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon - Leaf Green Version (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Sapphire Version (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Pokémon Sapphire Version</name>
		<desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokemon Sapphire. This entry in the Pokemon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokemon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokemon Sapphire is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokemon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokemon contests. With new Pokemon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokemon Sapphire takes the Pokemon experience to the next level.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pokemon - Sapphire Version (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puyo Pop # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Puyo Pop</name>
		<desc>Help Arle and Carbuncle make their way home! Take on all of the wacky characters you meet in challenging games of Puyo Pop so you can make your way through the land and back to safety. It's a mad scramble to erase Puyo, create chain combos, and fill up your opponent's playfield in this fast-paced puzzle game.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Puyo Pop # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Racing Gears Advance (U).gba</path>
		<name>Racing Gears Advance</name>
		<desc>Choose from 12 officially licensed supercars from top manufacturers including Dodge, Lotus, Chevy, Mitsubishi, GM and more. Kick it into gear and race like a pro as you power-slide through tough turns and take hidden shortcuts to reach the finish line. Feel the exhilaration of stopping another racer in their tracks with a well placed rocket. But be sure to upgrade your supercar and bring the right tires, as the Racing Gears League continues whether rain or snow. Team up with your friends for multi-player racing action.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Racing Gears Advance (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Orbital Media</developer>
		<publisher>Orbital Media</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rhythm Tengoku (Japan).gba</path>
		<name>Rhythm Tengoku</name>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Rhythm Tengoku (Japan)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060803T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>J.P. Room</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Music</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Riviera - The Promised Land (U).gba</path>
		<name>Riviera: The Promised Land</name>
		<desc>In Riviera: The Promised Land, you'll follow two fierce warriors--each armed with godly weapons--in a mission to defeat demons once and for all. The adventure included lets you experience more than 30 hours of role-playing gameplay, complete with minigames, multiple endings, and secret paths and items. The game's unique item system allows items to function differently depending on which characters equip them.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Riviera - The Promised Land (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advanced Wars  # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Robot Wars: Advanced Destruction</name>
		<desc>In just over 4 years the Robot Wars TV series has grown from cult status to become a massive worldwide phenomenon, with the BBC show now attracting a weekly audience of around four million viewers. Taking its cue from the latest series, this GBA Robot Wars game cranks up the action with new events, new robots, new arenas and a wide range of new game features.

The game brings together all the elements of the TV show - players can design and build their own robots, drawing upon a database of body parts, armour, engines, wheels and weapons. Once complete, battle can commence!

The game also features a quick start `pick up and play' function, so gamers can select from a range of pre-built robots, and get straight to the realistic 3D action.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Advanced Wars  # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crawfish Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>BBC Multimedia</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Advance # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Sonic Advance</name>
		<desc>The Story begins as Sonic goes to search for Eggman around the South Island, by collecting Chaos Emeralds. Sonic arrives in Angel Island and he sees a Robot named, Metal Knuckles, and Eggman built the Egg Rocket which will go in outer space, so Sonic goes in and finds Eggman. Later he finds Eggman and chases him outside and defeats him.

Bad Ending: After Sonic defeats Eggman, Sonic doesn't have enough chaos emeralds. He falls down to Earth and is caught by Tails in his Tornado.

Good Ending: After Sonic defeats Eggman, he collects all the chaos emeralds and he turns into Super Sonic and chases Eggman onto the moon for his first time. After Super Sonic defeats Eggman and flies off the moon, Tails, Knuckles, and Amy wondered what happened to Sonic, so Tails goes to search for Sonic a few days later. He finds Super Sonic who came from the moon, as Tails waves to him.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sonic Advance # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20011220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Advance 2 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Sonic Advance 2</name>
		<desc>Sonic Advance 2 is a 2D side-scrolling platform game, similar to earlier games in the series such as the first Sonic the Hedgehog. The player controls Sonic the Hedgehog, who can unlock Cream the Rabbit and her Chao, Miles "Tails" Prower, and Knuckles the Echidna after defeating Doctor Eggman in specific boss battles. A fifth character, Amy Rose, can be unlocked after completing all of the game with each character.[4] Each character has their own unique moves and abilities; for example, Cream and Tails can fly, while Amy can swing a hammer throughout levels.


Cream in a 3D "special stage"
In the tradition of past Sonic games, gameplay consists of moving quickly through levels, collecting rings and defeating enemies. Levels in the game are divided into seven "zones", each consisting of two acts of normal gameplay then a boss battle, where the player fights Doctor Eggman in order to stop Eggman from "building a Dr. Eggman Empire by kidnapping the animals and turning them into robots". The player collects rings as a form of health; when they are attacked by an enemy, their rings bounce in all directions. If they are hit by an enemy and have no rings, they lose a life. The player can also collect seven "special rings" to access "special stages", where Chaos Emeralds are found. "Special stages" are on a 3D plane, where the character tries to obtain a set number of rings before time runs out in order to collect a Chaos Emerald. After beating all zones and finding all seven Chaos Emeralds, an alternate final act is unlocked. When that act is beaten, a sound test feature and a boss time-attack feature are unlocked, along with the Tiny Chao Garden, where toys for Cream's Chao, Cheese,[4] can be purchased with rings earned in-game. Various mini-games can also be played in the Tiny Chao Garden.

Other game modes include a "time-attack" mode where the player tries to beat a specific act in the shortest amount of time, and a multiplayer mode, where players can race each other through unlocked acts.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sonic Advance 2 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030309T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Advance 3 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).gba</path>
		<name>Sonic Advance 3</name>
		<desc>The basic gameplay combines the traditional platforming elements of Sonic Advance, and the speed-orientated gameplay of Sonic Advance 2, to provide an experience similar to the original games. Sonic Advance 3 also introduced a new game feature called "Tag Action". Tag Action is similar to Knuckles' Chaotix: the player picks two characters and controls one while the other will just follow along controlled by the computer (or player two in multiplayer mode). Additionally, in a feature first seen in Knuckles' Chaotix the character can pick up the teammate by holding R, and then release them to use special abilities. Certain pairings, such as pairing Sonic and Tails or Amy and Cream, give the player access to the trick moves from the previous game.

At the start of the game, only Sonic and Tails are playable. By completing certain levels with Sonic as the team leader, Knuckles, Cream and Amy become playable.

The games features seven main levels (Route 99, Sunset Hill, Ocean Base, Toy Kingdom, Twinkle Snow, Cyber Track and Chaos Angel), each with their own "Zone Map". These maps have three acts which can be played in any order, but all three must be played before the boss can be fought. These maps also contain two mini-games in which extra lives can be earned. The player can change between maps by entering the "Sonic Factory". Here, the player can also change characters and access the level's "Chao Playground", which contains all the Chao found in that level. The player needs to find 10 per level in order to access the Special Stage and earn Chaos Emeralds.

Two additional levels follow Chaos Angel - the final boss, "Altar Emerald" (The shrine of the Master Emerald) and the extra boss, "Nonaggression", which can only be accessed when playing as Sonic after all seven emeralds have been collected.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sonic Advance 3 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Battle # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Sonic Battle</name>
		<desc>Who would win in a fight--Sonic, Tails, or Knuckles? You determine the answer in Sonic Battle, a game that pits Sonic and his friends against each other in furious arena combat. The game features eight playable characters, each with their own strengths and weaknesses, plus one mystery fighter to unlock. With three types of special attacks and ground, aerial, and defense fighting techniques, you can customize your character to suit your fighting style. Up to four friends can link their systems together using the Game Boy Advance Game Link cable for team battles, and then combine special attacks into devastating combos.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sonic Battle # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Pinball Party (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).gba</path>
		<name>Sonic Pinball Party</name>
		<desc>It's time to get the party started right with "Sonic Pinball Party" for the Game Boy Advance. Sonic The Hedgehog returns to the Game Boy Advance, with the ultimate handheld pinball experience, delivering fresh pinball boards filled with SONICTEAM characters and a huge assortment of multiplayer party games. With SONICTEAM characters from "Sonic The Hedgehog," "Samba de Amigo" and "Nights," "Sonic Pinball Party" challenges players to shoot, tilt, and flip their way through a slew of pinball boards, lightning fast mini-games and party games that promise to give gamers the pinball fix they've been craving!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sonic Pinball Party (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030717T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man - Mysterio's Menace (U) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Spider-Man: Mysterio's Menace</name>
		<desc>Set in New York, Spider-Man: Mysterio's Menace enables players to assume the role of Spider-Man as they take on super-villain Mysterio and his illusory tricks for control of Manhattan. Spider-Man must fight a slew of Mysterio's sinister conspirators and gadgetry to get to the bottom of their plot and free New York from Mysterio's mind-warping grip.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Spider-Man - Mysterio's Menace (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro 2 - Season of Flame # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Spyro 2: Season of Flame</name>
		<desc>Spyro 2: Season of Flame tells the story of Spyro's return to the Dragon Realms where he is surprised to discover that a mysterious enemy has stolen the Fireflies, the source of all dragon firepower, including Spyro's. Now it is up to everyone's favorite purple dragon to save the Fireflies before it is too late!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Spyro 2 - Season of Flame # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro Orange - the Cortex Conspiracy # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Spyro Orange: The Cortex Conspiracy</name>
		<desc>Spyro Orange is Vicarious Visions' first Spyro the Dragon title, taking the reigns after Digital Eclipse's GBA trilogy. For Spyro's fourth appearance on the Game Boy Advance, the development team has given the dragon a more traditional side-scrolling environment for his overworld instead of taking him back to his isometric exploits. But the scrolling platformer is only part of the experience. Spyro Orange focuses on dozens of mini-challenges for its gameplay, like a vertical shooter where Spyro floats around blasting sheep or collecting gems, a rapid-button-tapping challenge involving tug-o-war and ice cube creation, or driving around in a tank, or knocking out a series of bad guys in a Breakout-style challenge. The game supports link cable play for multiplayer challenges.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Spyro Orange - the Cortex Conspiracy # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Universal Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro - Season of Ice # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Spyro: Season of Ice</name>
		<desc>Dragons never seem to have had it too easy. They have always had to worry about dragon slayers, plus they usually get a bad rap for being destructive, and let's not even get started on what people say about their breath! Fortunately Spyro has generally avoided such negative opinions, but then again he hasn't always had it easy either. You'd think that after several death-defying adventures on the Playstation over the past few years, which included the defeat of the evil Sorceress, Spyro and his friends would be able to take some time off and enjoy a bit of a vacation at Dragon Shores. But with evil brewing and a new title on the way for the GameBoy Advance, which is due out in November, the gang shouldn't get too comfortable on the beach.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Spyro - Season of Ice # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha 3 (E) (M3) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 3</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 3, the third game in the Alpha series, has a total of 31 fighters, the most in the series so far. New characters include old favorites E. Honda, Blanka, Vega, Cammy, T. Hawk, Dee Jay, Juni and Juli. Some of the newest fighters on the block include a former Final Fight character (Cody, who has been in jail since the last Final Fight game, or so his clothing suggests), Karin Kanzuki and Rainbow Mika.

The major difference between this Alpha and the last two are the new play modes World Tour, Arcade, VS, Training and Entry.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Street Fighter Alpha 3 (E) (M3) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20021204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crawfish</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Summon Night - Swordcraft Story # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Summon Night: Swordcraft Story</name>
		<desc>Summon Night: Swordcraft Story is an RPG set in the strange world of Lyndbaum, a sacred land linked to four magical dimensions from which Summoners can call forth spirits called Guardian Beasts to do their bidding.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Summon Night - Swordcraft Story # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flight-Plan</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Summon Night - Swordcraft Story 2 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Summon Night: Swordcraft Story 2</name>
		<desc>In Summon Night: Swordcraft 2, the player is an orphan from the Colthearts clan raised by a Craftknight (a smith/warrior). The character aspires to be a Craftknight as well. The player character, either Edgar Colthearts or Aera Colthearts, who are Edge Fencers, find themselves at the site of an abandoned ruin where a violent Summon Beast named Goura is awakened. In order to protect their new family, Edgar/Aera is bound to a wild Summon Beast (stray summon) and embarks on a journey to reseal the ruins.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Summon Night - Swordcraft Story 2 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20061003T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flight-Plan</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bust-A-Move (USA) (En,Fr,Es).gba</path>
		<name>Super Bust-A-Move</name>
		<desc>Super Puzzle Bobble introduces some new elements to the series (and removes some others):

    Large bubbles are found in certain levels. Shooting a bubble of the same color at them makes every bubble in the level change into that color.
    In some levels, the pointer and the bubbles that are shot are of a very small size, enabling the player to shoot bubbles between small gaps. These bubbles grow into normal size after being clustered.
    Occasionally, a conveyor belt will surround the level. This makes bouncing off the ceiling and the walls significantly tricky, since the bubbles' trajectory will change upon bouncing.
    Levels do not always have the usual rectangular shape. Some of them are jagged or have walls inside them, which forces the player to change strategy.
    Small blocks appear in some levels. They change the bubbles' trajectories, much like walls, but they move down with the level and fall off when they touch the line.
    The pulley system introduced in Puzzle Bobble 4 is nowhere to be seen.
    Chain Reaction is only present in 2P battles, but it is completely optional.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Bust-A-Move (USA) (En,Fr,Es)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20011127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Dodge Ball Advance (Europe).gba</path>
		<name>Super Dodge Ball Advance</name>
		<desc>The year is 20XX and dodge ball has become the number one sport in the world. Teams from all over the world now compete in dodge ball tournaments to prove once and for all who is the best dodge ball team ever.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Dodge Ball Advance (Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Million</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Ghouls 'N Ghosts (U).gba</path>
		<name>Super Ghouls 'n Ghosts</name>
		<desc>As dauntless knight Arthur you are caught up in the most dangerous of quests! A spell has been cast upon the kingdom. Your fair maiden, Princess Prin Prin has been snatched up by the evil emperor. Only as Arthur can you get her back from the creatures of the undead that haunt the land. Test your courage and skill to the limit. You must keep up the quest. On your journey, your mightiest weapon of all awaits you... MAGIC!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Ghouls 'N Ghosts (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer></developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Advanced 2 - Mario World # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance 2: Super Mario World</name>
		<desc>Super Mario Advance 2 is a port of the 1991 SNES video game Super Mario World for the Game Boy Advance.

After saving the Mushroom Kingdom, brothers Mario and Luigi agree to take a vacation to a place called Dinosaur Land, where there are many types of dinosaurs. While resting in the beach, however, Princess Toadstool disappears. When Mario and Luigi wake up they try to find her and, after hours of searching, come across a giant egg in the forest. It suddenly hatches and out of it comes a young dinosaur named Yoshi, who then tells them that his dinosaur friends have also been imprisoned in eggs by evil turtles. Mario and Luigi soon realize that it must be the evil King Koopa Bowser and his Koopalings.

Mario, Luigi and Yoshi set out to save Princess Toadstool and Yoshi's dinosaur friends, exploring Dinosaur Land for Bowser and his Koopalings. To aid him, Yoshi gives Mario a cape as they begin their journey. Mario and Luigi continue to follow Bowser defeating the koopalings in the process and save all of Yoshi's dinosaur friends. They eventually make it to Bowser's castle, where they fight him in a final battle. They defeat Bowser and save the Princess, restoring peace to Dinosaur Land.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario Advanced 2 - Mario World # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20020211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Advance 3 - Yoshi's Island (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance 3: Yoshi's Island</name>
		<desc>Super Mario World 2: Yoshi's Island was ported by Nintendo R&amp;D2 to the Game Boy Advance as Yoshi's Island: Super Mario Advance 3 with added features.

A stork carries two babies across the sea, but the evil Magikoopa Kamek emerges, and steals Baby Luigi, and Baby Mario falls onto an island in the middle of the sea, called Yoshi's Island, home to all Yoshis. He lands on a green Yoshi, who was apparently taking a walk and Mario and the rest of the Yoshi gang must journey through the game's six worlds to rescue Baby Luigi and the stork back from Baby Bowser and Kamek. Throughout the quest, Kamek tries to stop Yoshi by transforming normal enemies with his magic, thus setting the stage for several boss fights.

When he finally reaches Bowser's Castle, Kamek demands that Yoshi gives back Baby Mario. Suddenly, Baby Bowser wakes up and tries to ride Yoshi, but Yoshi knocks him off. Kamek then enlarges Baby Bowser to a gigantic size, destroying most of the castle in the process. After fighting and defeating him, Bowser is reverted to his normal size and is unconscious. Kamek is horrified and says that they will return before flying off with Baby Bowser into the night.

Yoshi then frees the stork and Baby Luigi. The stork then flies the reunited twins far away to the village where their parents live. Here, it shows that Mario and Luigi's parents live in the Mushroom Kingdom in a house which is incidentally shaped like a Mushroom. Their parents then emerge from their home at dawn to see a pair of not quite new-born babies at their porch.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Mario Advance 3 - Yoshi's Island (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20020920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Advanced 4 - Mario Bros. 3 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance 4: Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
		<desc>Super Mario Advance 4 is a port of Super Mario bros. 3.

The game centers on the quest of Mario and Luigi to save the rulers of seven kingdoms from Bowser, the series' antagonist. The two brothers must travel across eight worlds to restore order to the Mushroom World. It built on the game play of previous Mario games by introducing new power-ups that augment character abilities, and established conventions that were carried over to future games in the series.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario Advanced 4 - Mario Bros. 3 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20031021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4-in-1 - GT Advance - Championship Racing &amp; GT Advance 2 - Rally Racing &amp; GT Advance 3 - Pro Concept Racing &amp; Moto GP (U).gba</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance 4: Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
		<desc>Super Mario Advance 4 is a port of Super Mario bros. 3.

The game centers on the quest of Mario and Luigi to save the rulers of seven kingdoms from Bowser, the series' antagonist. The two brothers must travel across eight worlds to restore order to the Mushroom World. It built on the game play of previous Mario games by introducing new power-ups that augment character abilities, and established conventions that were carried over to future games in the series.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/4-in-1 - GT Advance - Championship Racing &amp; GT Advance 2 - Rally Racing &amp; GT Advance 3 - Pro Concept Racing &amp; Moto GP (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20031021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy 4 Advance # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance 4: Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
		<desc>Super Mario Advance 4 is a port of Super Mario bros. 3.

The game centers on the quest of Mario and Luigi to save the rulers of seven kingdoms from Bowser, the series' antagonist. The two brothers must travel across eight worlds to restore order to the Mushroom World. It built on the game play of previous Mario games by introducing new power-ups that augment character abilities, and established conventions that were carried over to future games in the series.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Final Fantasy 4 Advance # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20031021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Advanced - Mario Bros. 2 + Mario Classic # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance: Super Mario Bros. 2</name>
		<desc>Super Mario advance is a remake of Super Mario Bros. 2.

At the beginning of each stage, the player is given a choice of four protagonists to control: Mario, Luigi, Toad, and Princess Peach, credited in the game as merely "Princess." Each character has different strengths; Mario is a well-rounded character; Luigi can jump the highest of the four; Toad can run and pluck vegetables the fastest but can't jump well; and Peach can jump the farthest, due to her ability to hover for a short time, though she is the slowest runner. All characters have the ability to increase the height of their jump by ducking briefly before they jump.

Unlike the previous and following Mario games, no enemies can be defeated by jumping on them. Instead, the player character must throw objects at enemies, such as vegetables plucked from the ground. Certain opponents can be picked up and thrown as well, and several levels feature blocks marked with the word "POW", which when picked up and thrown kill all the enemies on screen at impact, similar to the one in Mario Bros.

The game features a life meter, a then-unusual feature in the series. The player begins each stage with two points of health, represented by red hexagons, and can increase the number of health points in the meter by collecting mushrooms. Health can be replenished by floating hearts, which appear after a certain number of opponents have been defeated. The invincibility star from the previous game appears, with a player needing to collect five cherries to acquire it.

Each stage contains one or more hidden flasks of potion. When plucked and thrown, a potion creates a door to Sub-Space, an alternate world in which coins are collected instead of vegetables when plucked. The mushrooms used to increase the health meter can also be found here. The player automatically leaves Sub-Space after a short time. The coins collected are used in a slot machine mini-game played between stages. This mini-game is the chief means of obtaining additional lives. In addition to the mushrooms and slot machine coins, several Sub-Spaces are also used as warp zones; these involve the use of vases as pipes.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario Advanced - Mario Bros. 2 + Mario Classic # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20010321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monkey Ball Jr. # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Super Monkey Ball Jr.</name>
		<desc>The goal of the game is to maneuver a monkey trapped in a ball by tilting the labyrinth and reaching the goal at the end of the maze.

Like many other games of Super Monkey Ball series, the player has the option to choose Aiai, Meemee and Gongon. In multiplayer, two to four people can pick the same character.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Monkey Ball Jr. # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realism</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LEGO - Star Wars 2 - the Original Trilogy # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Super Robot Taisen: Original Generation 2</name>
		<desc>The battle rages on!

Peace slowly settles over the planet Earth after a brutal war against the alien armada. However, the world is not able to rest for long, as new forces emerge and threaten to bring Earth to it's knees once again. Use all the cunning and tactical skill you have to command the best and brightest mech pilots the world has ever seen in saving humanity from enemies bent on dominating the human race - or worse, annihilating it's very existence.

* Multiple branching pathways provide 50+ hours of strategy RPG gameplay!
* New allies, new enemies, and new mechs!
* Enhanced animations showcasing more extreme attacks!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/LEGO - Star Wars 2 - the Original Trilogy # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Banpresto</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Robot Taisen - Original Generation 2 (U) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Super Robot Taisen: Original Generation 2</name>
		<desc>The battle rages on!

Peace slowly settles over the planet Earth after a brutal war against the alien armada. However, the world is not able to rest for long, as new forces emerge and threaten to bring Earth to it's knees once again. Use all the cunning and tactical skill you have to command the best and brightest mech pilots the world has ever seen in saving humanity from enemies bent on dominating the human race - or worse, annihilating it's very existence.

* Multiple branching pathways provide 50+ hours of strategy RPG gameplay!
* New allies, new enemies, and new mechs!
* Enhanced animations showcasing more extreme attacks!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Robot Taisen - Original Generation 2 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Banpresto</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Street Fighter II Turbo - Revival (E) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II Turbo: Revival</name>
		<desc>Capcom's timeless Street Fighter® masterpiece conquers the Game Boy® Advance system. Choose from over 16 brawlers from the Street Fighter universe and execute special moves, and super combos to wreak havoc on your opponent and become the best street fighter in the world. Lightning fast animation, unbelievable graphics and Capcom's signature gameplay make Super Street Fighter II Turbo the most respected fighting game of all time.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Street Fighter II Turbo - Revival (E) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20011101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom Production Studio 3</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sword of Mana (USA, Australia).gba</path>
		<name>Sword of Mana</name>
		<desc>Sword of Mana is an enhanced remake of the original Game Boy game Seiken Densetsu.

At the beginning of the game, the player is able to choose to play as the male lead or as the female lead, both of whom are named by the player. They each have a different quest, but their plots remain similar. Notably, the remake adapted many elements from the original game, which had their origin in Final Fantasy, and favored elements traditional to Mana games (for example, the chocobo was replaced by cannon travel). One notable exception to this are moogles, which do appear in the game. Sword of Mana was made to resemble the graphical style of Seiken Densetsu 3, but the artwork rather resembles that of Legend of Mana.

The ring system from Secret of Mana is featured once again, allowing players to choose various options on the field screen. The day-and-night system introduced in Seiken Densetsu 3 also makes a return. Much like Legend of Mana, players can forge weapons, plant produce in an orchard, and read recorded events in the game's "Hot House" feature.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sword of Mana (USA, Australia)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brownie Brown</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tactics Ogre - the Knight of Lodis # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Tactics Ogre: The Knight of Lodis</name>
		<desc>Under the watchful eye of the Holy Lodis Empire, strange things are happening on the island of Ovis. Powerful forces have been set in motion, but their motives are masked by political intrigue. It is your mission to investigate these occurrences and discover the true intentions of those involved. The ending of the game will depend on the actions that the main character, Alphonse, takes. You will make many revelations as you proceed, but you must survive the unrelenting battles and cultivate your characters' abilities to unveil the ultimate truth.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tactics Ogre - the Knight of Lodis # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20020506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tales of Phantasia (USA, Australia).gba</path>
		<name>Tales of Phantasia</name>
		<desc>For young swordsman Cress Albane, it wasn't a typical day out hunting in the nearby woods. He had no hint of the tragedy unfolding back home. Battle in real time: The Linear Motion Battle System puts the emphasis on action as you attack your enemies without the use of menus. New game events, dialogue sequences, and other features enhance the adventure. Crack open the Monster Dictionary to view the strengths and weaknesses of the enemies you've met in battle. Players will want to collect data on them all. Use the innovative Cooking System to collect ingredients and recipes to brew up meals that restore your health and magic.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tales of Phantasia (USA, Australia)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken Advance (U) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Tekken Advance</name>
		<desc>Finally, the biggest, baddest bruiser of them all goes portable! And it's all here... the vicious combos, the killer graphics, and the greatest fighters. Practive your technique, remember to sidestep, and pray your skills are up to the challenge. Nothing compares to the massive bone crunching moves and brutal face-poundings of the King of Iron Fist Tournament.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tekken Advance (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20020128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past &amp; Four Swords (USA, Australia).gba</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past</name>
		<desc>Now you have a link to one of the greatest adventures in The Legend of Zelda series. The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past revives the classic SNES game on the Game Boy Advance and adds a new multiplayer mode. In a Link to the Past, Link travels between the light world and the dark world, conquering fierce monsters and uncovering Hyrule's deepest secrets along the way. Also included is Four Swords, which lets you play with up to three other players, slashing through dungeons and collecting rupees. Whether you choose solo or competitive play, The Legend of Zelda will keep you occupied with its brain-bending puzzles and fun swashbuckling action.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past &amp; Four Swords (USA, Australia)-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda - the Minish Cap # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: The Minish Cap</name>
		<desc>Link returns in an all-new Game Boy Advance adventure. When the sorcerer Vaati turns Princess Zelda to stone, the king of Hyrule sends Link on a quest that takes him to all-new locations. Using the power of a mystical hat called the Minish Cap, Link must travel through a fantastic world rife with new items, puzzles, and bosses. As Link, you can shrink down to either battle large enemies from within or find secret items. You can also unlock items and solve puzzles by fusing together magic relics.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Zelda - the Minish Cap # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT (U) (M3).gba</path>
		<name>TMNT</name>
		<desc>Leonardo, training in the woods, is then given the mission to find a mystic amulet by Master Splinter's orders. After he finds the amulet, it is revealed that Splinter was telling the story of how they stopped the four Stone Generals, and asks Donatello and Michelangelo to continue it. Once, Raph infiltrated Max Winters' tower (as Nightwatcher), and eavesdropped on a conversation with Winters and Karai. Raph was then defeated by one of the Stone Generals. Later on, Leo found out that Raph was the Nightwatcher, and a chase ensued, ending up with Leo being ambushed and captured by the Foot. Raph, feeling guilty, decides to go after the Foot. He then encounters one of the Stone Generals, and defeats her, with the help of Don and Mikey. The turtles then head off to rescue Leo, and they achieve this goal, right before the temple self-destructs. The turtles then go to Max Winter's tower, and Winters tells his story of being an immortal warrior named Yaotl. Yaotl was planning to activate a portal to another world, but it released 13 monsters into the earth. Yaotl became immortal, but it also turned his generals to stone. Yaotl then planned to stop his mistakes and his immortality by waiting for the portal to come again, and send all the monsters back to whence they came. He also made his generals come to life, but they remained in stone form. The Stone Generals wanted to live forever, so they turned on Yaotl. The turtles, however, managed to defeat the Generals, the portal opened, and the monsters returned to their dimension. Yaotl then thanks the turtles and dies happy and free from guilt. After the story, the turtles all realize the importance of family and grow closer as not only a family but also as a team.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/TMNT (U) (M3)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam</name>
		<desc>Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam delivers a totally unique skateboard experience focused on head-to-head racing. The game allows players to feel the breakneck speed of downhill competition as they tear up the world's steepest terrains while performing tricks and outmanoeuvring opponents in such locations as San Francisco, Machu Picchu and Hong Kong. Taking on the role of Tony Hawk or one of nine characters, players compete in time-based challenges in one of three gameplay modes, including race, trick and slalom.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Impact</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to the award winning PSX and N64 title, Tony Hawk 2 adds heaps of new tricks, as well as those from the original, and a complete roster of all the greatest skaters worldwide. Fly through some of the greatest skate parks in the world, or create your own, and share them with your mates. You can also create your own skater, with a choice of clothing and official skateboards. Improved graphics and a choice of alternative or hip-hop music add to the endless options and full on action.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (U) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3</name>
		<desc>You may not be able to live like the legend, but now you can skate like him. Skate as the legendary Tony Hawk or choose from a dream team of 12 top pro skaters, including old favorites like Lasek, Thomas, Muska, and Steamer, as well as new talent like Gilfberg, Caballero, Koston, and Mullen. Or enjoy full customization abilities with the enhanced Create-a-Skater (now including female skaters) and the Skatepark Editor. Travel from L.A. to Tokyo, Suburbia to Skater's Island performing challenges and meeting goals. New moves include the Revert, which allows you to link vert tricks, and flatland tricks such as Caspers, the Primo, and Handstand Manual. If you're good, you can even unlock hidden pro footage.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer></developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players></players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20160219T054915</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4</name>
		<desc>THPS4 is the fourth game in Activision's ever popular franchise.

The main feature of this game is it's redesigned career mode. When beginning a level, you have all the time in the world to skate around, perform tricks, get a feel for the level, without the hassel of any goals or time limits. When you're ready to attempt a goal, simply find a pro skater, talk to him, then receive the goal, similar to Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX. Goals are similar to the previous games, such as collect SKATE, get a certain amount of points, transfer over this and grind that. There are new goals, however, such as collecting the word COMBO while doing one big combo. Miss a trick, and goal fails. Once all regular goals are accomplished, you can attempt the Pro Goal, which is specific to each skater, and is extremely hard.

All the major skaters are here, including Tony Hawk, Bob Burnquist, Steve Caballero, Kareem Campbell, Rune Gilfberg, Eric Koston, Bucky Lasek, Bam Margera, Rodney Mullen, Chad Muska, Andrew Reynolds, Geoff Rowley, Elissa Steamer and Jamie Thomas.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Underground (U).gba</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Underground</name>
		<desc>Activision's definitive skateboarding game returns on the PlayStation 2, GameCube, Xbox, Game Boy Advance and PC with Tony Hawk's Underground. In a departure from former games in the series, Underground gives players the chance to take an ambitious non-pro skater from an unknown, to superstar status. For the first time in the series, players will be able to get off their board and explore the expansive levels on foot, or in a vehicle. Customize the look of your skater, your skater's tricks, and even create custom skateparks. Tony Hawk's Underground features nine sprawling courses, as well as a level of freedom and customization that is unprecedented in the popular series.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tony Hawk's Underground (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20031027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Underground 2 # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Underground 2</name>
		<desc>You've been chosen by Tony Hawk to compete against Bam Margera's team in the World Destruction Tour. In an all-new storyline, Tony Hawk's Underground 2 takes you to skateparks around the world, where you can spray your custom tag, slap stickers, and even create new skate lines. Now you can play as yourself, as your teammates, or as more than 20 special skaters. If you're feeling nostalgic for older Tony Hawk games, you can try Classic mode, which challenges you to accomplish your favorite goals, such as Secret Tape and High Score.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tony Hawk's Underground 2 # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20041004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turbo Turtle Adventure (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Turbo Turtle Adventure</name>
		<desc>Help Turbo Turtle win his freedom to once again swim the sea. Trapped on the 'Isle of Mazes' you must guide Turbo Turtle through deceitful labyrinths and nasty traps. Collect keys to unlock doorways, avoid the super magnets and utilize the turbo boost feature to try and beat your fastest time. This innovative title blends the basic balancing act of Super Monkey Ball with the mind-bending key-and-switch puzzles found in the Zelda games.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Turbo Turtle Adventure (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iridon Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Games</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Brain Games (U).gba</path>
		<name>Ultimate Brain Games</name>
		<desc>Part of the Telegames Ultimate series of handheld pick-up games. Ultimate Brain Games includes a collection of favorite strategy challenges. Playable games include Chess, Checkers, Backgammon, Mahjong, Dominoes, 4-in-a-Row, Sink the Ships, and Reversi. Features include 2D and 3D graphics, 2-player link play, and downloadable multiplayer.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ultimate Brain Games (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cosmigo</developer>
		<publisher>Telegames</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Card Games (U).gba</path>
		<name>Ultimate Card Games</name>
		<desc>Card game compilation pack from Telegames. There are nine classic card games: Hearts, Spades, Euchre, Canasta, Bridge, Cribbage, Go Fish, Gin Rummy, and Crazy Eights. There are also three casino-style games: Poker, Blackjack, and Video Poker. To cap things off, the development team included 15 different styles of solitaire games, including Klondike, FreeCell, Canfield, Pyramid, Golf, Spider, Baker's Dozen, Bristol, Castle, Aces Up, Barons, Eagle Wing, Eight Off, Calc, and Betsy Ross. If you don't know the rules to specific games, there's in-cartridge "how to play" tutorials that can be pulled up at any time. And, like Ultimate Brain Games, Ultimate Card Games features cartridge SRAM to save statistics and games in progress.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ultimate Card Games (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20111114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cosmigo</developer>
		<publisher>Telegames</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./V-Rally 3 (U).gba</path>
		<name>V-Rally 3</name>
		<desc>Strap yourself in for the most intense and lifelike rally racing you've ever experienced. Introducing V-Rally 3, the next evolution in the leading rally racing franchise that has sold over 5 million copies worldwide.

Everything about V-Rally 3, from the highly detailed cars to the meticulously handcrafted tracks, creates unprecedented racing realism. V-Rally 3... It leaves everything else in the dust!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/V-Rally 3 (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Velez &amp; Dubail</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Tennis (U).gba</path>
		<name>Virtua Tennis</name>
		<desc>Directly translated from the popular arcade stand-up, Virtua Tennis offers a light-year jump from the Pong-style tennis of yesteryear. Sporting rich 3-D graphics, crisp animation, and realistic sound effects, you'll swear you're courtside at a grand slam. But, thanks to the game's simple controls, you won't have to spend years at a tennis camp just learning a backhand. The game features hard-top, grass, and clay surfaces, all with distinct ball-bounce and sound responses. Choose one of eight internationally ranked tennis pros and play against advanced computer opponents, or plug an extra controller in and play a friend head to head. Just as in real championships, ball boys, chair umps, and even spectators react to your game.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Virtua Tennis (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Altron</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wade Hixton's Counter Punch (USA, Europe).gba</path>
		<name>Wade Hixton's Counter Punch</name>
		<desc>After his car breaks down, Wade Hixton stumbles upon the little-known town of Big Piney. Wade, however, gets himself into even more trouble, as town members challenge him to fight. Step into Wade's shoes as he boxes nine different fighters, each with a unique personality and fighting technique. Give yourself a competitive advantage by upgrading your attacks, purchasing new moves, and even paying off characters to assist you during matches.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Wade Hixton's Counter Punch (USA, Europe)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inferno Games</developer>
		<publisher>Destination Software</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land 4 (UE) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Wario Land 4</name>
		<desc>The gameplay of Wario Land 4 (which is generally similar to that of Wario Lands 2 and 3) allows for some open-endedness as well as some order of difficulty. There are four main passages in addition to the Entry Passage and "Final" Golden Pyramid: the Emerald, Topaz, Ruby, and Sapphire Passages, in order of difficulty. The Emerald Passage is themed around nature. The Ruby Passage is themed around mechanics and technology. The Topaz Passage is themed around toys, games, and other "playtime" ideas. The Sapphire Passage is themed around horror and danger, prominently involving ghosts and the like.

There are four levels in a passage. To progress to the next level in a passage, a player has to find the Keyzer in the previous level (a Keyzer is a floating key-nosed creature that promptly disappears after the player uses it). After the four levels comes a Mini-game Shop and the Boss Room. To enter the Boss Room, the player must find the four pieces of the passage's namesake gem in each level (a total of four gems and 16 pieces). Also, a player can find a CD in each level, which unlocks music in the CD Room. Upon entering a level, one has unlimited time to find treasure, beat up enemies, and such. Enemies, when defeated, give coins and health orbs. After collecting a full bar of health orbs, the player receives one extra heart (out of 8). However, the player can't return to the pyramid (and thus have all of their treasure saved) until they open the portal again via a Frog Switch. Upon hitting the switch, a time limit (which varies depending on the game's difficulty setting and level itself) is placed, and many blocks in the level appear or disappear. For some levels, this results in a rush back to the portal the same way the player came. In others, totally new areas are exposed. If Wario fails to reach the portal within the time limit, he begins to lose coins. Once all of his coins are gone, he is kicked out of the level (as if he had lost all of his health) and is left with no treasure.


Wario about to fight the first boss, Spoiled Rotten.
At the end of each passage, Wario encounters a boss room. He must destroy a boss within a set time limit to win the treasure within the boss rooms (if Wario takes too long but manages to win before the limit is up, some treasure may be withheld). Before each battle, Wario will enter a hall way consisting of two doors. One is a shop which uses mini-game coins as currency; in it, Wario can buy various power-ups and weapons that deal damage to the boss right before the battle.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Wario Land 4 (UE) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20011119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Ware Inc. # GBA.GBA</path>
		<name>Wario Land 4</name>
		<desc>The gameplay of Wario Land 4 (which is generally similar to that of Wario Lands 2 and 3) allows for some open-endedness as well as some order of difficulty. There are four main passages in addition to the Entry Passage and "Final" Golden Pyramid: the Emerald, Topaz, Ruby, and Sapphire Passages, in order of difficulty. The Emerald Passage is themed around nature. The Ruby Passage is themed around mechanics and technology. The Topaz Passage is themed around toys, games, and other "playtime" ideas. The Sapphire Passage is themed around horror and danger, prominently involving ghosts and the like.

There are four levels in a passage. To progress to the next level in a passage, a player has to find the Keyzer in the previous level (a Keyzer is a floating key-nosed creature that promptly disappears after the player uses it). After the four levels comes a Mini-game Shop and the Boss Room. To enter the Boss Room, the player must find the four pieces of the passage's namesake gem in each level (a total of four gems and 16 pieces). Also, a player can find a CD in each level, which unlocks music in the CD Room. Upon entering a level, one has unlimited time to find treasure, beat up enemies, and such. Enemies, when defeated, give coins and health orbs. After collecting a full bar of health orbs, the player receives one extra heart (out of 8). However, the player can't return to the pyramid (and thus have all of their treasure saved) until they open the portal again via a Frog Switch. Upon hitting the switch, a time limit (which varies depending on the game's difficulty setting and level itself) is placed, and many blocks in the level appear or disappear. For some levels, this results in a rush back to the portal the same way the player came. In others, totally new areas are exposed. If Wario fails to reach the portal within the time limit, he begins to lose coins. Once all of his coins are gone, he is kicked out of the level (as if he had lost all of his health) and is left with no treasure.


Wario about to fight the first boss, Spoiled Rotten.
At the end of each passage, Wario encounters a boss room. He must destroy a boss within a set time limit to win the treasure within the boss rooms (if Wario takes too long but manages to win before the limit is up, some treasure may be withheld). Before each battle, Wario will enter a hall way consisting of two doors. One is a shop which uses mini-game coins as currency; in it, Wario can buy various power-ups and weapons that deal damage to the boss right before the battle.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Wario Ware Inc. # GBA-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20011119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yggdra Union - We'll Never Fight Alone (USA).gba</path>
		<name>Yggdra Union: We'll Never Fight Alone</name>
		<desc>Ruled by a royal family said to be descendants of the gods themselves, Fantasinia is a prosperous and peaceful land -- until the peace is shattered by the invading forces of the Empire of Bronkia. Led by the young emperor Gulcasa, who seized control of the Empire in a brutal coup d?etat, Bronchia's Imperial Army cuts a bloody swath through the people of Fantasinia and the Royal Armies of King Ordeene. Amidst the chaos, a young woman escapes from the besieged capital of Partina -- a woman with innocence in her face, and a sword in her hand. The girl?s name is Princess Yggdra, the last surviving member of the royal family; the sword is the Gran Centurio, a legendary blade once wielded by the founder of Fantasinia, and passed down through generations of royalty. Fleeing to to a remote valley at the southern tip of the continent, Yggdra meets up with Milanor, the charismatic leader of a band of thieves, and readies herself for a war of liberation.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Yggdra Union - We'll Never Fight Alone (USA)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yu-Gi-Oh! - The Eternal Duelist Soul (U) [!].gba</path>
		<name>Yu-Gi-Oh! The Eternal Duelist Soul</name>
		<desc>The most accurate, advanced version of Duel Monsters arrives! The ultimate duel simulator based on the hit Trading Card Game and Television series! Duel against dozens of opponents from the TV show or challenge your friends. Import cards from the Official TCG to boost your deck. Complete your card collection and create the ultimate deck to enter the World Championship Tournament!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Yu-Gi-Oh! - The Eternal Duelist Soul (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20021015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
